

Apache Calcite – Pune/Noida			
Candidate Name	Gaurav B. Chavan		
Current Company	Datametica		
Current Designation	Software Engineer		
Current Location/Native	Pune		
Education	BE		
Experience	4.2 Years		

• Have 1+yrs experience in apache calcite.

Gauray B. Chavan

A/p-Karad,tal-Karad,Dist.-Satara.Pincode-410115

Mobile no : 7709620355 / 7349688587 Email Id : Chavangaurav366@gmail.com

Date of Birth: 17-10-1994

Career Objective:

To secure a position in the organization which offers me an opportunity to learn and evolve myself, such that my growth is that of the organization and to be an asset to the organization.

Summary Of Experience

4.2 Years of Experience in software development and Unit Testing.

Strong work Experience in Application Development based on J2EE enterprise solutions using Spring, CoreJava, JDBC, Servlets, JSP, Struts, Hibernate, mysql, javascript, ajax, jquery, Angularjs, Calcite, IBM Datastage, BigQuery and Json.

Technical Skills

Primary Skills	Java
Operating Systems	Windows, Linux
Languages	Java, Groovy
Client/server Technologies	Servlet 2.5 , JSP 2.0, Apache 5.5, Apache 6.0
Frameworks	Spring, Hibernate, Struts
Database	Mysql
Configuration Tools	SVN 1.7
Development Tools	Eclipse 3.4, Jasper Reports, IntelliJ
Scripts	JavaScript, Ajax, Jquery, Angularjs

Educational Qualification:

Exan	nination	Board/University	Institute	Percentage	Year
	BE	Shivaji	KIT college of Engineering,	66.26	2015-16
			Kolhapur		
	Diploma In	M.S.B.T.E	Government Polytechnic,	78.32	2012-
	Computer Tech.		Solapur.		2013
	SSC	State Board	Tilak High school, karad.	89.27	2009-
					2010

Professional Experience

Currently working in DataMatica Solutions Pvt. Ltd, Pune from June 2019. Worked in **Diksha Technologies, Bangalore** as a '**Software Engineer**', from December, 2017 to till 26 April 2019. Worked in **Greeman Software Solutions Pvt Ltd, Bangalore** as ' **Java Developer**' from July,2016 to December, 2017. Worked on Institute project, "College Issue tracking system" from Sep 2015 to May 2016.

Project Undertaken

1. Project Name: RavenETI

Team Size: 15

Description: RavenEtl is a product where Datastage jobs converted into Equivalent Bigquery. Firstly we are extracting the properties of stages supported by datastage. By using calcite we are creating relNodes in form of relational algebra. And converting the relNodes in BigQuery. Here we are supporting conversion from various databases like Oracle, Teradata, DB2 etc. to equivalent Bigquery.

My Responsibilities:

Worked On the Extraction of parallel and sequence jobs.

Worked on mainly Modeling of DB2 stage. Worked on multiple function support.

Environment : Groovy, Calcite, Gradle, BigQuery, DB2, Teradata, Oracle.

2. Project Name : ACADEMY

Team Size: 5

Description: This website is used for management of PES University Bangalore. All the process which are running in the college are managed by this websites, including management of data, Exams, attendance, Seating allocation of students, generating forms, faculty student management and many more.

My Responsibilities:

Worked in Generating 7 types of forms based on allocation. In Evaluation Assigning thefaculties.

IP Restriction and Barcode Generation.

Environment : Java 9, Spring, JDBC Template, JSP, Wildfly, MySql, Ajax, JQuery, Javascript, Json.

3. Project Name: Digitization

Team Size: 3

Description: This website is used to Evaluation of exams. Digitization is mainly focusing on digital evaluation and generate the all required reports such as Results which reduces the manual efforts.

My Responsibilities:

Worked mail sending functionality for sending mail to faculties on daily basis. Evaluation Summery Functionality.

Environment: Java 9, Spring, JDBC Template, JSP, Wildfly, MySql, Ajax, JQuery, Javascript, Json.

4. Project Name: Elearning Portal

Team Size: 4

Description: This website is purely based on online learning portal, here admin has all the rights. For example if some particular academy would like to register their course. Then they need to make some payment and then upload their courses. Once admin And academy uploads some courses then while student registration they need make Some payment for their selected courses so that they can learn through online and Registered students get notification, assignment and certificate as well through online. Learnezy Project contains following modules:

- 1. Admin Module.
- 2. Academy Module
- 3. Student Module

My Responsibilities:

Sms Gateway Integration.

Sitemap Implēmentations. Environment : Java 1.6, JSP, Struts 1.3, Servlet, Tomcat 5.0, MySql, Ajax, JQuery, Javascript, Json.

4. ProjectName:ERP

Team Size: 4

Description: This is a web application for maintaining all the process automatically. This software will reduce all the manual work and provides the data security in various processes like Hr, Sales, Purchase, and Productionetc.



HRModule :inthismoduleHRwillupdatetheexpense,salarycalculation,sendingpayslip and track leave of employees.

My Responsibilities

- Responsible to develop Hrmodules with all the submodules including Leave module, expense module, Payslip generation, salary calculation.
- Responsible for giving demo for HR module and making changes if require.

Environment used:	Spring.	Hibernate.	MvSal.	JOuery, Java.

DATE:	
PLACE:	(GAURAV CHAVAN)